<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Capital Solutions]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Capital Solutions]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/capsol/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>What We Do

•	We help great companies seeking capital across ASEAN, India and Australia find  the right investors. 
•	For Venture Capital, we focus on pre-Series A, A and B and for Private Equity and Debt funding our expertise is in finding investors for USD 3- 30 million. 
•	We strategically work with leading venture capital funds to identify financing opportunities within their portfolio companies that have solid traction, proven management teams, strong investor support, great technology and large target markets who can offer investors superior risk-adjusted returns.
•	 We help Family Offices and High Net Worth individuals who want to invest in companies, oftentimes where there is a recognised lead anchor investor.  
•	We also do Secondaries, helping early investors to find exits.

Based in Singapore, we are a seasoned, thoughtful, consultative, goal orientated and relationship driven team. 
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/3f9d6217-d1ec-4238-98b4-8b4dc88c0638/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3f9d6217-d1ec-4238-98b4-8b4dc88c0638</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>See What Clients Say About Us

"I have worked with Carl and Jason on few occasions now and I see them as true partners to the entrepreneur ( and investors in some cases as I have observed ) and they go way beyond their scope in ensuring that first of all the opportunity is fundable and then ensuring it gets funded. Given their diversity across finance and legal gives them an edge combined by a boutique approach to targeted approach rather than carpet bombing"
Anurag Srivastava, Co-Founder/ CEO SpaceMatrixGroup, Co-Founder Jungle Ventures, Co-Founder OneAnimation 

“Carl & Jason are an outstanding team who ensure client satisfaction at all times by getting the job done!”
Vince Tallent, Chairman & CEO, fastacash. Fintech 100: Leading Global Fintech Innovators, Red Herring Top 100 Global, SBF: Top 20 Hottest StartUps 
 
"Carl and Jason were an integral part of Booktracks Series A fundraising. Their professionalism and network of investors where very impressive. Most importantly they understand their investor profiles and the companies they work with to find a match. No time wasting, within 1-2 months we had held the investor meetings and closed the investment for interested parties. Can't recommend them enough"
Mark Cameron, Co-Founder/ Director, Booktrack

"Carl and Jason are a thoroughly professional team who are always accommodating and helpful. Their connectivity and network is extensive and I have always found them to give excellent advice. I have personally known Carl for almost ten years and he has advised me on many of my investments. I have also known Jason for a couple of years and have worked with both of them on several transactions. I would not hesitate to recommend them."
JM Chanrai, of the Kewalram Chanrai Group 

“Carl has been instrumental to work with as our start-up made the journey from seed round to private equity and institutional support.  Carl is a delight to work with, full of ideas and contacts.”
Frank Lavin, Founder/ CEO, ExportNow, inter alia former U.S. Ambassador to Singapore,  Undersecretary for International Trade - U.S. Department of Commerce, Lead trade negotiator for China


“Carl, Jason and their team  are result-oriented, very experienced, and provide outstanding practical  advice and service... Working with them was a pleasure, especially as they engaged with us as if they were part of our team.  Their excellent network of contacts enables them to punch way above their relatively small size.”
Bharat Dube, Founder/ CEO, SIPI

“We have benefited greatly from the range of services provided by Capital Solutions. Both Carl and Jason have been extremely understanding of our requirements, provided support and advice as required and have access to key individuals and organisations who are actively investing in companies seeking growth capital.”
Vikram Aggarwal, Founder/ CEO, eat2eat

“A firm of client focused consultants with a balanced personal and professional approach”
BS Mangat, Founder/ CEO, FTMSGlObal

“With Carl we have found a valuable partner that is trustworthy, result oriented and above all works in your interest.”
Tobias Meister, Founder/ CEO, AURESO
“ETP is a leading technology provider to Omni-Channel Retailers in Asia
Pacific, India and the Middle East. At ETP we have worked closely with Carl
for over 5 years now and it has been a pleasure working with him. Carl
helped us find the right investor and raise significant capital. He ran the
process very professionally keeping in view both the Investor and Investee's
goals and working closely with both to align them. He is insightful and has
high integrity, yet focusses on getting a positive outcome in specific
period of time. We intend to continue engaging Carl in our future endeavors.”
Naresh Ahuja, Founder/ CEO, ETP
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/49776916-00b3-4a03-a3a5-5de498a78d6f/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">49776916-00b3-4a03-a3a5-5de498a78d6f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>TEAM 

Carl Athayde. Co-Founder & Managing Partner, Marketing & Deal Origination

Prior to Capital Solutions, Carl founded CAadvisory Pte Ltd in 2010,, a Singapore-based boutique firm that introduced Founders to investors who provided Growth Capital. He is also a Corporate Advisor and selectively Board Observer to a number of growing Asian companies including fastacash,SpaceMatrix Group, FTMS, ETP,  eat2eat, Novosol, Aureso and SIPI.  

He previously worked as a senior banker over 19 years at Credit Suisse, ANZ, RBS, ABN AMRO and Standard Chartered in both the Institutional and Private client segments, in HongKong and Singapore.

Carl studied at the University of Illinois, U.S.A (master’s in management), the Tata Institute of Social Sciences, India, (master’s in personnel management), and St. Xavier’s College, India, (B.A. sociology and economics).  He attended the Wharton SMU management program, and completed relevant CMFAS modules. Carl was invited to join the Executive Board of Dana-Asia, a pan-Asia Pacific organization that assists donors in their Philanthropy, where he briefly served as  Chairman, Audit and Risk committee.


Jason Edwards. Advisor , Investor development  & Deal Closing

Prior to founding Alternative Investment Advisors, Jason was the General Counsel of Clearwater Capital Partners, a multibillion dollar Asian focused private equity fund that had a team of 6 lawyers. He was a member of the management committee and the investment committee.

Before that he was a partner with the international law firm Baker & McKenzie, having worked in both its Hong Kong and Bangkok office. He was the first foreigner to be made a partner in Baker McKenzies's Bangkok office, the largest law firm in Thailand, in more than 20 years. Before coming to Asia he was a Senior Associate with Clayton Utz, a national law firm in Australia.

He as worked as a lawyer for over 20 years, with more than 16 years in Asia advising on alternative investments. He is admitted to practice in England and Wales, Hong Kong and Australia.



Access to Resources:  As required, we have access to an excellent pool of Lawyers, Accountants, Auditors, Analysts, Operating Partners and Industry Experts
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/4072ec80-d2f4-46e7-af35-8c167f8695d9/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4072ec80-d2f4-46e7-af35-8c167f8695d9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
Live Deals
 
Below is a selection of some of the recent deals we are currently working on. In addition, we also have a number of Secondary Trades available:

	Sector	Deal Size (USD mln)	Stage	Capital Type
1	Big data	25	Pre Series B, Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
2	Marketing automation and Analytics	10		Convertible debt, Equity
3	Animation	10	Series B	Equity
4	Social payments	5	Pre IPO	Convertible debt, Equity
5	Customer engagement, Analytics and Marketing platform	7	Pre Series B, Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
6	F&B - restaurants	3	Series B/ PE	Convertible debt, Equity
7	Software	5	Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
8	Software	2	Series A	Convertible debt, Equity
9	Consumer Internet	2	Pre IPO	Convertible debt, Equity
10	F&B tech	3	Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
11	Education	5	Series C/ PE  	Convertible debt, Equity
12	Various	30	Secondaries	Equity



If you are an Investor and wish to know more on these deals please email carl@capsol.sg



</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/ed647af5-fb88-4d84-8ea3-42161f663594/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ed647af5-fb88-4d84-8ea3-42161f663594</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Recent Deals

Below is a selection of some of the recent deals we have closed:

Raised USD 10 million of convertible debt for a category leader across APAC in design services.

Raised OVER USD 6 million of convertible debt plus warrants for a leading education provider of professional courses and degrees across APAC. To date WE have raised over USD 15 million for the company.    

Raised over USD 8 million in successive rounds from pre Series A through A and B rounds for a global enabler of payments along with digital content through social networks and messaging platforms. 

Arranged equity growth capital for a global leader that uses its patented technology to transform the way people read though the addition of sound to an e-book or other digital content

Arranged equity growth capital for APAC’s leading brand monitoring,  investigation and enforcements company focused on helping root out illegal commerce on the internet.

Arranged equity growth capital for technology and trading company at the forefront of clean energy transportation across APAC

Arranged equity growth capital for a leading customer engagement, analytics and marketing platform in F&B.

Arranged debt funding for a leading F&B technology company that provides enterprise software to the world’s largest hotel chains 

Arranged post seed and Series A equity growth capital for a fast-growing SaaS company developing the future technology eco-system for the automotive retail industry.

</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/6fc27f3e-738e-4bb6-b389-7c16806831c3/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6fc27f3e-738e-4bb6-b389-7c16806831c3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>CONTACT US

Email: carl@capsol.sg
Mobile: +65 9621 0195

Corporate Address:

A Singapore registered company, Registration No XXXXX


DISCLAIMER

CA: J to review

Xxxxx is a company incorporated in the Republic of Singapore with Registration No:xxxx. The information contained herein is for information only and is not a recommendation or solicitation to buy or sell any security or other product or service, an official confirmation of any transaction or an official statement of xxx. Any unauthorized use, reproduction, or dissemination of company documents is prohibited. Neither xxx nor any of its subsidiaries or affiliates shall assume any legal liability or responsibility for any incorrect, misleading or altered information contained herein. Nothing on this website is intended to constitute legal, tax, securities or investment advice, or opinion regarding the appropriateness of any investment. Counterparts are advised to seek independent professional advice so they are aware of any and all risks.

 
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/a15dfbe3-3a5c-4e47-9306-3db904b2b0d1/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a15dfbe3-3a5c-4e47-9306-3db904b2b0d1</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>