<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Capital Solutions]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Capital Solutions]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/capsol/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>What We Do

•	We help great companies seeking capital across ASEAN, India and Australia find  the right investors. 
•	For Venture Capital, we focus on pre-Series A, A and B and for Private Equity and Debt funding our expertise is in finding investors for USD 3- 30 million. 
•	We strategically work with leading venture capital funds to identify financing opportunities within their portfolio companies that have solid traction, proven management teams, strong investor support, great technology and large target markets who can offer investors superior risk-adjusted returns.
•	 We help Family Offices and High Net Worth individuals who want to invest in companies, oftentimes where there is a recognised lead anchor investor.  
•	We also do Secondaries, helping early investors to find exits.

Based in Singapore, we are a seasoned, thoughtful, consultative, goal orientated and relationship driven team. 
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/3f9d6217-d1ec-4238-98b4-8b4dc88c0638/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3f9d6217-d1ec-4238-98b4-8b4dc88c0638</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>TEAM 

Carl Athayde. Co-Founder & Managing Partner, Marketing & Deal Origination

Prior to Capital Solutions, Carl founded CAadvisory Pte Ltd in 2010,, a Singapore-based boutique firm that introduced Founders to investors who provided Growth Capital. He is also a Corporate Advisor and selectively Board Observer to a number of growing Asian companies including fastacash,SpaceMatrix Group, FTMS, ETP,  eat2eat, Novosol, Aureso and SIPI.  

He previously worked as a senior banker over 19 years at Credit Suisse, ANZ, RBS, ABN AMRO and Standard Chartered in both the Institutional and Private client segments, in HongKong and Singapore.

Carl studied at the University of Illinois, U.S.A (master’s in management), the Tata Institute of Social Sciences, India, (master’s in personnel management), and St. Xavier’s College, India, (B.A. sociology and economics).  He attended the Wharton SMU management program, and completed relevant CMFAS modules. Carl was invited to join the Executive Board of Dana-Asia, a pan-Asia Pacific organization that assists donors in their Philanthropy, where he briefly served as  Chairman, Audit and Risk committee.


Jason Edwards. Advisor , Investor development  & Deal Closing

Prior to founding Alternative Investment Advisors, Jason was the General Counsel of Clearwater Capital Partners, a multibillion dollar Asian focused private equity fund that had a team of 6 lawyers. He was a member of the management committee and the investment committee.

Before that he was a partner with the international law firm Baker & McKenzie, having worked in both its Hong Kong and Bangkok office. He was the first foreigner to be made a partner in Baker McKenzies's Bangkok office, the largest law firm in Thailand, in more than 20 years. Before coming to Asia he was a Senior Associate with Clayton Utz, a national law firm in Australia.

He as worked as a lawyer for over 20 years, with more than 16 years in Asia advising on alternative investments. He is admitted to practice in England and Wales, Hong Kong and Australia.



Access to Resources:  As required, we have access to an excellent pool of Lawyers, Accountants, Auditors, Analysts, Operating Partners and Industry Experts
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/4072ec80-d2f4-46e7-af35-8c167f8695d9/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4072ec80-d2f4-46e7-af35-8c167f8695d9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
Live Deals
 
Below is a selection of some of the recent deals we are currently working on. In addition, we also have a number of Secondary Trades available:

	Sector	Deal Size (USD mln)	Stage	Capital Type
1	Big data	25	Pre Series B, Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
2	Marketing automation and Analytics	10		Convertible debt, Equity
3	Animation	10	Series B	Equity
4	Social payments	5	Pre IPO	Convertible debt, Equity
5	Customer engagement, Analytics and Marketing platform	7	Pre Series B, Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
6	F&B - restaurants	3	Series B/ PE	Convertible debt, Equity
7	Software	5	Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
8	Software	2	Series A	Convertible debt, Equity
9	Consumer Internet	2	Pre IPO	Convertible debt, Equity
10	F&B tech	3	Series B	Convertible debt, Equity
11	Education	5	Series C/ PE  	Convertible debt, Equity
12	Various	30	Secondaries	Equity



If you are an Investor and wish to know more on these deals please email carl@capsol.sg



</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/ed647af5-fb88-4d84-8ea3-42161f663594/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ed647af5-fb88-4d84-8ea3-42161f663594</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Recent Deals

Below is a selection of some of the recent deals we have closed:

Raised USD 10 million of convertible debt for a category leader across APAC in design services.

Raised OVER USD 6 million of convertible debt plus warrants for a leading education provider of professional courses and degrees across APAC. To date WE have raised over USD 15 million for the company.    

Raised over USD 8 million in successive rounds from pre Series A through A and B rounds for a global enabler of payments along with digital content through social networks and messaging platforms. 

Arranged equity growth capital for a global leader that uses its patented technology to transform the way people read though the addition of sound to an e-book or other digital content

Arranged equity growth capital for APAC’s leading brand monitoring,  investigation and enforcements company focused on helping root out illegal commerce on the internet.

Arranged equity growth capital for technology and trading company at the forefront of clean energy transportation across APAC

Arranged equity growth capital for a leading customer engagement, analytics and marketing platform in F&B.

Arranged debt funding for a leading F&B technology company that provides enterprise software to the world’s largest hotel chains 

Arranged post seed and Series A equity growth capital for a fast-growing SaaS company developing the future technology eco-system for the automotive retail industry.

</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/6fc27f3e-738e-4bb6-b389-7c16806831c3/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6fc27f3e-738e-4bb6-b389-7c16806831c3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>CONTACT US

Email: carl@capsol.sg
Mobile: +65 9621 0195

Corporate Address:

A Singapore registered company, Registration No XXXXX


DISCLAIMER

CA: J to review

Xxxxx is a company incorporated in the Republic of Singapore with Registration No:xxxx. The information contained herein is for information only and is not a recommendation or solicitation to buy or sell any security or other product or service, an official confirmation of any transaction or an official statement of xxx. Any unauthorized use, reproduction, or dissemination of company documents is prohibited. Neither xxx nor any of its subsidiaries or affiliates shall assume any legal liability or responsibility for any incorrect, misleading or altered information contained herein. Nothing on this website is intended to constitute legal, tax, securities or investment advice, or opinion regarding the appropriateness of any investment. Counterparts are advised to seek independent professional advice so they are aware of any and all risks.

 
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/capsol/a15dfbe3-3a5c-4e47-9306-3db904b2b0d1/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a15dfbe3-3a5c-4e47-9306-3db904b2b0d1</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 14:58:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>